hungryroot.com 2019-03-17

# Privacy Policy | Hungryroot

Privacy Policy

We value your privacy. This policy explains our privacy practices for hungryroot.com and services provided by Hungryroot, Inc. By visiting this website, you are accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of other websites linked to on our site.

Last Updated: October 1, 2014

Information We Gather or Receive

Hungryroot will not sell or disclose your name, email address or other personal information to third parties without your explicit consent, except as specified in this policy. Hungryroot may require additional information, such as billing and payment information (including billing address, telephone number, credit card information), a telephone number, and/or a physical address. Credit card information on an account may be stored and used for billing purposes.

Hungryroot automatically receives and records some information from your browser when you visit the site, such as your IP address, cookies and data about which pages you visit on the site through the use of log files provided by our third-party tracking-utility partners. This information helps us analyze and understand how the site works for customers and visitors, and provide a more personalized experience for members and visitors.

Hungryroot may receive or collect information (for example: email address) about a person who is not yet a registered Hungryroot customer in connection with certain Hungryroot features, including but not limited to: a non-customer subscribing to a Hungryroot newsletter or a non-customer requesting Hungryroot near them.

Hungryroot uses the information described in this policy to provide and improve our services, for billing and payments, for identification and authentication purposes, to contact members or interested parties, and for general research and aggregate reporting.

Hungryroot's Terms of Use require all account owners to be at least 18 years of age (or have the permission and supervision of a responsible parent or legal guardian), therefore, this policy does not discuss use of our site or services by minors.

Controlling Your Information

We want you to have control over your own information, so Hungryroot gives you the choice of providing, editing or removing certain information.

You may change or correct your Hungryroot account information at any time, such as your email address, phone number or credit card information.

For various reasons, Hungryroot may contact you about our services or your activity. Some of these messages are required, transaction-related message to customers. Other messages are not required, such as our newsletters, and you can control which optional messages you choose to receive by changing your settings in your account.

If you no longer wish to use Hungryroot's services or receive service- related messages, please email help@hungryroot.com.

Messages from Hungryroot

In order to fulfill orders and keep you informed, Hungryroot will contact you. Typically, messages are delivered by email and SMS messages, and every account is required to keep a valid email address and phone number on file to receive messages. In some situations, Hungryroot may contact you by telephone or physical mail in order to provide you with information about products and features you may find of interest or to provide you with customer support.

Some messages from Hungryroot are service-related and required for customers. Examples of service-related messages include, but are not limited to: a confirmation of your order or correspondence with the Hungryroot support team. These messages are not promotional in nature. You may not opt-out of receiving service-related messages from Hungryroot, unless you close your account.

As a customer, Hungryroot may also send you messages related to certain features on the site or your activity. Hungryroot may also send you news or updates about changes to our site or services. By default, customers will receive these messages via email.

Hungryroot offers optional email newsletters. When you register for an account, or choose to subscribe, you will receive newsletters from us. Newsletters are available to both customers and non-customers. Customers may subscribe or unsubscribe from optional newsletters by following the instructions contained in the newsletter emails.

What Information We Share

Hungryroot will never sell or disclose your name, email address or other personal information to third parties without your explicit consent, except as specified in this policy.

Hungryroot may release your personal information to a third-party in order comply with a subpoena or other legal requirement, or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law; prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or investigate or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or violations of Hungryroot's Terms of Use.

Hungryroot uses other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf, and we need to share your information with them to provide products and services to you. Examples include but are not limited to fulfilling orders, processing payments, handling billing disputes and collections, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and providing customer service.

In some cases, Hungryroot may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, member information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Hungryroot will transfer information about you if Hungryroot is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Hungryroot will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

When you a load a page on Hungryroot that has a social plug-in from a third-party site or service, such as a Like or Send button, you are also loading content from that third-party site. That site may request cookies directly from your browser. These interactions are subject to the privacy policy of the third- party site.

We can only speak for ourselves; this policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Hungryroot does not own or control, or individuals that Hungryroot does not employ or manage. If you provide your information to others on Hungryroot or throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to the use or disclosure of the information you provide to them. Hungryroot does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. Hungryroot is not responsible for the privacy or security practices of other websites on the Internet, even those linked to or from the Hungryroot site. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

We reserve the right to transfer information (including your personal data) to a third party in the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, receivership or transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of our company provided that the third party agrees to adhere to the terms of our Privacy Policy and provided that the third party only uses your personal data for the purposes that you provided it to us. You will be notified in the event of any such transfer and you will be afforded an opportunity to opt-out.

Cookies & Tracking Technologies

Hungryroot uses a variety of technologies to help us better understand how people use our site and services. Hungryroot may partner with third-party services who may use various tracking technologies, such as browser cookies or Flash cookies, to provide certain services or features. These technologies allow a partner to recognize your computer each time you visit Hungryroot, but do not allow access to personally identifiable information from Hungryroot. Hungryroot does not have access or control over these third-party technologies, and they are not covered by our privacy statement.

Data Retention

Hungryroot will retain your information only for as long as is necessary or your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you no longer want Hungryroot to use your information to provide you services, you may close your account. Hungryroot will retain and use your information as necessary to improve your experience with our products and services, comply with law enforcement and resolve disputes.

You may inform us of any changes or requests in regards to your personal data, and in accordance with our obligations under local data protection law, we may update or delete your personal data accordingly.

Privacy Policy Changes

Hungryroot reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it periodically. We’ll communicate changes by posting a notice on the site. If we make material changes to this policy you will be notified here, by email, or other places Hungryroot deems appropriate.

Contact Hungryroot

If you have questions or suggestions you can contact Hungryroot's support team by sending an email to help@hungryroot.com.
